https://jenkinhill.net/privacy-statement.html

Jenkin Hill Internet
Web development & consultantancy
HomeServicesWebsite designMobile-friendly designAccommodation websiteseCommerceWebsite maintenanceWebsite makeoverRatesContactVirtueMart supportExtended portfolio
Privacy statement
Privacy statement for jenkinhill.net
Cookies
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information which enables us to provide you with improved services. This does not involve personal information. We also use cookies to help us compile anonymised aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. More about cookies
Email
If you choose to telephone or email Jenkin Hill Internet from this website we confirm that we consider your personal data to be private and will not pass any information, including your email adress, to any third party unless with your specific permission and only in connection with your business.
Legal information
Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies, and Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation). GDPR regulations
This privacy policy relates solely to this Website.
Latest update: May 18, 2018
Jenkin Hill Internet, 34 Laxfield Way, Lowestoft, Suffolk NR33 7HH, UK
Tel: +44(0)7949 606116Email: design@jenkinhill.net
Privacy statement
© 2020 Jenkin Hill Internet
The EU introduced a ridiculous law which requires us to tell you that - like almost every other website - we use cookies to enable the site to work. No data about you is stored. The EU requires us to ask you if you accept this.
I accept Decline
More information
